export const week1Items = [
  {
    id: 0,
    answer: "Jurisdiction",
    question:
      "The word _________ is used to mean the area covered by a single legal system and set of laws.",
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    answer: "Police",
    question:
      "are responsible for discovering who has carried out a specific criminal offence and for collecting evidence that will convince a court that the person in question really did commit the offence.",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    answer: "Litigation",
    question: "Court action under the civil law is known as.",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    answer: "Plaintiff",
    question: "the person who initiates the court action is known as the",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    answer: "Common law and Statute law",
    question: "the two main sources of law in England and Wales.",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    answer: "Common Law",
    question:
      "is essentially traditional law that is not written down, but which depends on the judgement of judges over the centuries.",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    answer: "Legislation",
    question:
      "statute law is law laid down by Acts of Parliament. It is often referred to as?",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    answer: "Criminal Law",
    question:
      "is a system of laws concerned with punishment of individuals who commit crimes.",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    answer: "Civil Law",
    question:
      "is the part of a country's set of laws which is concerned with the private affairs of citizens, e.g. example marriage and property ownership.",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    answer: "Law",
    question:
      "is a set of rules which a particular country or community recognizes as regulating the actions of its members and which it may enforce by the imposition of penalties.",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    answer: "Prime Minister",
    question: "In Singapore, The head of the government is the_______",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    answer: "Congress",
    question: "in the USA, the legislature is known as",
  },
];

export const week2Items = [
  {
    id: 0,
    answer: "Ethics",
    question:
      "is concerned with what is good for individuals and society and is also described as moral philosophy. The term is derived from the Greek word ethos which can mean custom, habit, character or disposition. Ethics covers the following dilemmas: how to live a good life. Ethics is a system of moral principles",
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    answer: "consequences",
    question:
      "Computer systems perform tasks and the way they perform tasks has moral _________",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    answer: "James Moor",
    question:
      "paper published in 1985: What is Computer Ethics? As a field of academic research, computer ethics had its beginnings in the early 1980s.",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    answer: "Consequentialism",
    question: "sometimes called utilitarianism",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    answer: "equality",
    question: "In favor of Kant’s theory is that it assumes ______",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    answer: "conduct",
    question: "Most professional bodies have codes of ______",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    answer: "invisible",
    question:
      "An essential fact about computers is that computer operations are ",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    answer: "Utilitarian",
    question:
      "theory says that a good outcome brings ‘the greatest benefit to the most significant number of people.",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    answer: "Computers",
    question:
      "are used by businesses to speed up routine work, such as calculating payrolls.",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    answer: "Code of Conduct",
    question:
      "is a set of rules around behavior for the employees to follow within an organization.",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    answer: "Law",
    question:
      "A rule of conduct or action that a nation or a group of people agrees to follow",
  },
];
export const week3Items = [
  {
    id: 0,
    answer: "Crime Prevention",
    question:
      "Hacking can also be conducted on behalf of law enforcement agencies for the purposes of ______________ and detection, or increasingly, counter-terrorism.",
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    answer: "Software",
    question:
      "can be downloaded to crack passwords or serial numbers for software installation, or to bypass other protections and security measures",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    answer: "Viruses",
    question:
      "can be transmitted by downloading a program from another computer, or can be present on a disk.",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    answer: "Trojan Horse",
    question:
      "is a program in which malicious or harmful code is disguised inside some apparently harmless programming or data",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    answer: "Hacking",
    question:
      "is an act of compromising digital devices and networks through unauthorized access to any account or computer system.",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    answer: "Worm",
    question:
      "is a self-replicating program that entails deleting portions of a computer’s memory, thus creating a ‘hole’ of missing information.",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    answer: "Bugs",
    question:
      "Hackers expose ______ in some software to alert software developers so that they can provide a solution.",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    answer: "Hacker",
    question:
      "is a person who uses computers to gain unauthorized access to data.",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    answer: "Trojan Bombs",
    question: "are programs that can be activated on a particular date.",
  },
];

export const week4Items = [
  {
    id: 0,
    answer: "Identity Theft",
    question:
      "involves taking credit card numbers, national insurance or social security numbers, bank account details, addresses, and other personal data.",
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    answer: "Cybercrime",
    question:
      "is any criminal activity that involves a computer, networked device, or network.",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    answer: "Corporate Espionage",
    question:
      "is unlawful theft which involves the theft of these corporate assets or trade secrets from competitors.",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    answer: "Data Diddling",
    question:
      "is a type of cybercrime in which data is altered as it is entered into a computer system, most often by a data entry clerk or a computer virus.",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    answer: "Piggybacking",
    question:
      "refers to tapping into communication lines and ‘riding’ into a system behind a legitimate user with a password.",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    answer: "Embezzlement",
    question:
      "is one of the most common crimes and refers to the fraudulent appropriation of funds by a person to whom those funds have been entrusted.",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    answer: "Cybercriminals",
    question:
      "are individuals or groups who use technology to commit malicious activities on digital systems, computers, or networks.",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    answer: "Computer Fraud",
    question:
      "8.	Pyramid schemes, chain letters, sales of counterfeit goods, etc., are an example of _____",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    answer: "Sofware Piracy",
    question:
      "is a major area of criminal activity involving the distribution of illegal software and other intellectual products.",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    answer: "Computer Forensics",
    question:
      "specialists retrieve evidence from the hard disks of such computers.",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    answer: "Computer Forensic",
    question: "11.	The field of collecting evidence from computers is called ",
  },
];

export const week5Items = [
  {
    id: 0,
    answer: "passwords",
    question:
      "One of the simplest and most widely used computer security measures involves the use of _______ which authenticate authorized users and allow access to a system or network.",
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    answer: "Encryption",
    question:
      "a process of converting data into a form called cipher that unauthorized receivers cannot easily understand. ",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    answer: "Decryption",
    question:
      "is the process of converting encrypted data back into its original form, so it can be understood.",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    answer: "Firewall",
    question:
      "software gives access only to trusted Internet (IP) addresses and scrutinizes data for irregularities or signs of danger.",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    answer: "Access Control Software",
    question:
      "It restricts users, individually identified by password, to only those files they are authorized to use.",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    answer: "Biometrics",
    question:
      "These technologies work by sampling `unique` biological features, such as the voice, the pattern of blood vessels in the retina, or fingerprints",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    answer: "Audit Control Software",
    question:
      "this type of software can also be used specifically to browse through vast amounts of financial transactions, looking for signs of any abnormal activity, such as a high number of `correction entries`, which often indicates the trial-and-error approach of fraud.",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    answer: "Anti Virus",
    question:
      "programs also prevent infected files from being downloaded (whether from a disk or an e-mail attachment) and prevent viruses from inserting themselves into a computer system.",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    answer: "Security Policies",
    question: "also need to include management policies for checking employees",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    answer: "Security Policies",
    question:
      "it involves decisions about appropriate network access and authority levels and the implementation of password systems, disaster recovery plans, and other security procedures.",
  },
];
